fouani.com 2012-12-21

# Privacy

##   
1\. What personal information does Fouani collect through this website and how does Fouani collect it?

We only collect personal information that  **YOU**  want to provide to us or that is needed to provide (and improve) our service to you. We collect direct personal information such as name, address and e-mail address as well as indirect information such as cookies, connection and system information.

You may want to give us your e-mail address, name, telephone number etc. so that we can provide you with information on our products; enter you into our competitions or surveys; or just keep you updated about exciting Fouani developments that you are interested in.

Alternatively, you may want to develop your career with Fouani and apply for job vacancies by posting your CV on our on-line recruitment sites.

## 2\. How does Fouani keep your personal information secure?

Fouani takes all necessary measures to keep your personal information private and secure. Only authorized Fouani Group staff, Third Party companies (i.e. service providers) staff or our business partners' authorised staff (who have contractually agreed to keep all information secure) have access to your personal information. All Fouani staff who have access to your personal information are required to adhere to the Fouani Group Privacy Policy and all third-party employees who have access to your personal information have signed non-disclosure agreements. In addition, contracts are in place with third-party companies that have access to your personal information, to make sure this information remains secure. To ensure your personal information is protected, Fouani maintains a secure IT environment and has the appropriate measures in place to prevent unauthorised access. 

## 3\. What purposes does Fouani use your personal information for?

Your personal information will be used for the purposes for which you provided it to Fouani. It will also be used to administer, support and obtain feedback on the level of our services and to prevent breaches of security, the law or our contract terms.

Return to top

## 4\. How can you see, check, change or delete the Personal Information you send to us?

You have the right in a number of countries to ask companies (such as Fouani) to provide you with all the information it stores on you. Certain national laws may require you to pay a small charge for this activity. You may also have your personal information deleted, corrected or revised by sending an e-mail to [support@fouani.com](mailto:support@fouani.com).

Return to top

## 5\. What happens to my personal information if I participate in an on-line survey from Fouani through this website?

From time to time, we may ask our website visitors to answer survey questions. Surveys generally will relate to the content of the website, our products or categories of products. We may ask for age or age ranges, gender, and/or other non-personally identifiable information. For the purposes of these surveys, we may add information obtained from cookies to your survey answers but no personally identifiable information will be requested. The personal information collected is not tied to any personal information that you may already have given to us. Personal information gathered from polls and surveys are for Fouani internal use only but aggregated information (not capable of personally identifying anyone) may be shared with others.

## 6\. What is One-Time Registration?

In order to make the registration process easier, we use a one-time registration tool across many Fouani websites. With this tool, when you register with our website, this information can be automatically made available to you for registration at other Fouani website(s). Your personal information remains protected and we always ask for your express consent or "Opt-In" to receive information from Fouani website(s) before you are added to any mailing list.

## 7\. Can Fouani change the terms of this Privacy Notice?

Fouani will occasionally make changes and corrections to this Privacy Notice. Please check this Privacy Notice regularly to see the changes and how these may affect you.

Return to top

## 8\. Which address is available for me to contact Fouani if I have other questions regarding my personal information?

The address is: [support@fouani.com](mailto:support@fouani.com), **  
Head Office:  
**11/13 WareHouse Road,  Apapa, Lagos 

Return to top

## 9\. IMPORTANT – Why do I have to accept the terms of this Privacy Notice?

Fouani is a global company that uses the Internet to collect and process your personal information. This naturally involves the Processing and transmission of your personal information across borders.

This Privacy Notice provides you with all information necessary (in an easily accessible way) to make an informed choice as to whether to use this website and to send your personal information to Fouani or not.

Therefore, by browsing this website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our Processing of your  ** _indirect_**   personal information (cookies, connection and system information) in the manner set out in this Privacy Notice.

If you ask us to provide a certain service to you (i.e. a competition, newsletter or new product details etc.) we will need additional ** _direct_**  personal information ( _name, address and e-mail address_ ) from you. In this case, we will ask you for your express consent to collect and use this personal information. This personal information will be used only for the purposes for which you gave it to us.

Return to top
